<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Gassa Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://Gassa.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Gassa.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-06-16T17:03:37-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://Gassa.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Yin Yan]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[gassa0617@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code_Navitation_with_Vim]]></title>
    <link href="http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2015/02/25/code-navitation-with-vim/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-25T16:55:26-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2015/02/25/code-navitation-with-vim</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Cscope gets its list of what to index from a file called cscope.files.
find <code>pwd</code> -name &ldquo;<em>.c&rdquo; -o -name &ldquo;</em>.h&rdquo; -o -name &ldquo;*.cpp&rdquo; > cscope.files</p>

<p>Building Cscope Database:
cscope -b -q -k</p>

<p>ctags -L cscope.files
<a href="http://www.fsl.cs.sunysb.edu/~rick/cscope.html">http://www.fsl.cs.sunysb.edu/~rick/cscope.html</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Paparazzi Analysis]: Getting Started With Jpapabench 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2014/04/27/jpapabench1/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-27T02:57:28-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2014/04/27/jpapabench1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I am currently working on a project that related to <a href="http://wiki.paparazziuav.org/">Paparazzi</a>.
Surprisingly, There are only few material available online. I decide to document all my exploration
here. most of the things I am writing here is mainly from my code analysis,
<a href="http://wiki.paparazziuav.org/wiki/Developer_Guide">Paparazzi wiki page</a> and its is related Java
version project <a href="http://d3s.mff.cuni.cz/~malohlava/projects/jpapabench/">Jpapabench</a>.</p>

<p>Jpapabench is a Java version of Paparazzi to provide a realistic application benchmark for
evaluation variouse Java Virtual Machine (JVM), especilly for Real-time JVM. Since the code base of
Paparazzi have been grown dramaticly to adapt to more wild hardware driver support, it is more
easier to start with Jpapbench, it mirrors the function of Paparazzi, change the cyclic execution
into tasks and execute them in seperated threads. Therefore, I decide to start with Jpapabench
first.</p>

<hr />

<p>In Jpapabench, There are three sets of tasks, Autopilot, FBW(fly-by-wire) and sensing simulations as
shown in</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper'><img src="http://Gassa.github.io/images/jpapabench-pic/task-dependencies-flow.jpg" title="Jpapabench task dependency" ><span class='caption-text'>Jpapabench task dependency</span></span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2014/04/22/who-am-i/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-22T13:27:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Gassa.github.io/blog/2014/04/22/who-am-i</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>See you Wordpress!!!</h2>

<p>After two hours setting up, I finally have my new blog established with Octopress, and I can claim I am done with Wordpress. It really drove me crazy. I never satisfied with its page layout and display format, especially when I embedded some code snippets. In addition, I am also missing some of you older articles, when I moving my previous blog from wordpress.com to my own VPS hosting. Now I am happy with Octopress, it is easy to set up, and its markdown engine is pretty intuitive, almost zero learning curvy required.</p>

<h2>Integrate Octopress with Github Page</h2>

<p>The most convenient parts of Octopress is its integration with <a href="http://github.com">Github</a>. I can host my blog on Github pages, and edit it at anywhere as long as I have access to internet and git. On Octopress Documentation, there is an <a href="http://octopress.org/docs/deploying/github/">step-by-step instruction</a> that guide you to set up connection between your local repo and remote repo.</p>

<p>First of all, create a git repo under github user account. To synchronize with remote repo, there is a configuration task,</p>

<figure class='code'><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class=''><span class='line'>rake setup_github_pages</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>The rake task will ask you for a URL of the Github repo. Copy the SSH or HTTPS URL from your newly created repository (e.g. <code>git@github.com:username/username.github.io.git</code>) and paste it in as a response.</p>

<p>Then, use <code>rake generate</code> to get the initialize default site at local, run <code>rake deploy</code> to push the site content to your repo and corresponding Github Page (e.g <code>username.githit.io</code>).</p>

<h2>Repo configuration</h2>

<p>After getting everything working, I became interested in how all of the magic happens. The answer is in the <code>.git/config</code> file, when we run <code>rake setup_github_pages</code> and provide git repo url, <code>rake</code> clone the git repo as remote origin and push the generated site content into repo&rsquo;s master branch, then create another branch called &ldquo;source&rdquo; in same repo, all Octopress source code and blog markdown source code are pushed into origin source.</p>

<p>Thus, I can use <code>rake generate &amp;&amp; rake deploy</code> to commit and push code to my blog repo&rsquo;s master branch, and run <code>git pull origin source</code> and <code>git push origion source</code> to pull the my repo&rsquo;s source code to any local repo, edit them and push them back to remote repo. Another taking away is <code>rake -T</code> that displays all availible option for <code>rake</code></p>

<h2>What&rsquo;s this blog about?</h2>

<p>The purpose of this blog is to record the solution and thoughs realted to my work and study. The topic will mainly lay in Linux kernel development, internal Android system analysis, some programming language concepts and some my research project related stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
